A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Business Interests, Series C FA312
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Center, Inc. (RCI)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Radio-Keith-Orpheum (RKO), 1939-1944 (Box 90, Folder 681)
    General, miscellaneous correspondence re Radio-Keith-Orpheum (RKO). RKO a holding company, with RKO Radio Pictures its main subsidiary; problems created by World War II; Rockefeller involvement in RKO. Correspondents include George Schaefer, Nelson A. Rockefeller, B. P. Turnbull.
    205.11F
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Metropolitan Square - Miscellaneous Contracts - Renewals of Architects' Contracts, 1935-1940 (Box 90, Folder 682)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases, 1931-1936 (Box 91, Folder 683)
    Inquiries, problems; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. re liquor sales; re tenant problems. Comments on conditions of tenants; aid to tenants. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Nelson A. Rockefeller, B. P. Turnbull, H. Robertson, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    205.13
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases, 1937-1941 (Box 91, Folder 684)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases, 1942-1960 (Box 91, Folder 685)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - American Cyanamid, 1934-1947 (Box 91, Folder 686)
    Relations with tenant.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Associated Press, 1937-1961 (Box 91, Folder 687)
    Terms of lease; 1961 renewal.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Chase Bank, 1933-1946 (Box 91, Folder 688)
    Lease negotiations; question of exclusive banking operation; relations.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Chemical Bank and Trust Company, 1945-1947 (Box 91, Folder 689)
    Negotiations for lease.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Consolidated Oil Corporation, 1935-1945 (Box 92, Folder 690)
    Negotiations; ownership of 55 Liberty Street building; former offices of Sinclair Oil Co.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Eastern Air Lines, 1940-1947 (Box 92, Folder 691)
    Publicity re lease; mural by Cromwell.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - German Building, 1933-1934 (Box 92, Folder 692)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Pan American Proposals, 1935-1941 (Box 92, Folder 693)
    Plans for Latin American clubs and centers; none developed.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Time, 1937-1955 (Box 92, Folder 694)
    Lease negotiations.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Italian Building, 1932-1938 (Box 92, Folder 695)
    Proposal for Italy building; trouble with Italian agent re compensation. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., H. Robertson, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Thomas M. Debevoise.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - British Empire Building - Lord Southborough Correspondence, 1931-1935 (Box 92, Folder 696)
    Proposal for British Empire Building; English reception; opening of building. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - French Building, 1931-1951 (Box 92, Folder 697)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. letter to French Ministry of Foreign Affairs re purpose of building French Building; lease to French syndicate; problems with Bosworth. Syndicates' progress in getting tenants. Re Cartier Property purchase proposal; contract arrangements with French syndicate. Arrangements for building decor. Relations with tenants. Correspondents include H. Robertson, P. C. Cartier, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise, J. R. Todd.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - French Building - Dedication Ceremonies, 1932-1933 (Box 92, Folder 698)
    President Herriot's speech.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - French Building - Henri Charpentier, 1934-1941 (Box 92, Folder 699)
    Restauranteur at Maison has problems and a grievance against Rockefellers.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Standard Oil and Frank Shattuck Company, 1933-1940 (Box 93, Folder 700)
    Renegotiations for lease in Radio Corporation of America (RCA) Building; plans for new Esso building. Arrangements for restaurant in Esso building. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, B. P. Turnbull, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - Standard Oil and Frank Shattuck Company, 1933-1940 (Box 93, Folder 701)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - United States Rubber Company, 1939-1954 (Box 93, Folder 702)
    Lease negotiations; arrangements for lease of new building. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, Charles O. Heydt, Thomas M. Debevoise, B. P. Turnbull.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Leases - United States Rubber Company - Equitable, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 703)
    Financial arrangements for United States Rubber Building.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Theme and Decoration, 1931-1933 (Box 93, Folder 704)
    Discussion of general theme for Center; selection of muralists; various suggestions re artwork, inscriptions. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s opinion of Friedlander's work. Nelson A. Rockefeller's suggestions re artists. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John R. Todd.
    205.14
    Separated Materials note
    The original material has been separated to Box 94 A, Folder 704 A.
    The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original archival material is restricted. Photocopies of the originals are available for scholarly access.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Theme and Decoration, 1934-1960 (Box 93, Folder 705)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    The original material has been separated to Box 94 A, Folder 705 A.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Diego Rivera, 1932-1950 (Box 94, Folder 706)
    Public reactions, pro and con, to dismissal of Rivera. Artists' applications for jobs; some letters of Diego Rivera and Frieda Kahlo to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller before split. Later comments. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
    205.14A
    The original material has been separated to Box 94 A, Folder 706 A.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Diego Rivera - Office Letter and Statement, 1932-1933 (Box 94, Folder 707)
    Arrangements with Rivera; Nelson A. Rockefeller letters asking for changes; Rivera's refusal. Protest from Mexico re destruction of mural.
    The original material has been separated to Box 94 A, Folder 707 A.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Diego Rivera - Clippings, 1932-1950 (Box 94, Folder 708)
    Newspaper clippings re Rockefeller Center, Inc. mural and artist; Rivera's death in 1957.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Murals - Jose Sert, 1933-1943 (Box 94, Folder 709)
    Negotiations with Sert; comments on his murals in RCA Building. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jose Sert, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    205.14B
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Franchise for Tunnels, 1932-1936 (Box 94, Folder 710)
    Negotiations with city for underground tunnels and vaults in Center area. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Thomas M. Debevoise.
    205.16
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Laying of Cornerstone, July 2, 1932, 1931-1932 (Box 94, Folder 711)
    Dedication of British Empire Building; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. short speech; British attendance and comments.
    205.15
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Laying of Cornerstone, July 2, 1932 - Dedication Exercises, 1931-1932 (Box 94, Folder 712)
    For Radio Corporation of America Building. Not held as planned due to strike among workers.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Laying of Cornerstone, July 2, 1932 - Dedication of British Empire Building (Box 94, Folder 713)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Theme and Decoration, 1931-1933 (Box 94A, Folder 704A)
    The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original archival material is restricted. User copies are found in Box 93, Folder 704.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Theme and Decoration, 1934-1960 (Box 94A, Folder 705A)
    The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original archival material is restricted. User copies are found in Box 93, Folder 705.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Diego Rivera, 1932-1950 (Box 94A, Folder 706A)
    Public reactions, pro and con, to dismissal of Rivera. Artists' applications for jobs; some letters of Diego and Frieda Kahlo to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller before split. Later comments. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
    The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original archival material is restricted. User copies are found in Box 94, Folder 706.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Diego Rivera - Office Letter and Statement, 1932-1933 (Box 94A, Folder 707A)
    The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original archival material is restricted. User copies are found in Box 94, Folder 707.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Terminal and Jersey Transportation, 1929-1939 (Box 95, Folder 714)
    Proposals and suggestions for studies. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt.
    205.17
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Terminal and Jersey Transportation - Lockwood Greene Contract, 1934 (Box 95, Folder 715)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - National Broadcasting Company, 1933-1948 (Box 95, Folder 716)
    Invitations; requests for tickets; friendly comments. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Charles O. Heydt.
    205.18
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - National Broadcasting Company - M. H. Aylesworth, 1932-1938 (Box 95, Folder 717)
    Friendly relations with Rockefellers; resignation to join United Press.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - National Broadcasting Company - Center Theater Television Studio, 1950-1953 (Box 95, Folder 718)
    Arrangements.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - National Broadcasting Company (NBC) Color Television City, 1954-1955 (Box 95, Folder 719)
    Proposed broadcasting center; political complications; abandonment of plan. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, David Sarnoff, G. S. Eyssell.
    205.18A
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rainbow Room and Grill, 1934-1961 (Box 96, Folder 720)
    Selection of orchestra; success of charity program for opening night. Management problems. 1943 closing; reopening. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, F. W. Darling, John Roy.
    205.19C
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rockefeller Center Lunch Club, 1934-1961 (Box 96, Folder 721)
    Plans for limited-membership luncheon club on 65th floor. Club operations; nomination of new members. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Thomas M. Debevoise, B. P. Turnbull, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    205.19A
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Restaurant Facilities - Miscellaneous, 1933-1949 (Box 96, Folder 722)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd comments re proposed restaurants in Center; plans for restaurants and clubs; circus atmosphere for Rainbow Room area. Plans for cafeteria; reports on operations. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, Frank W. Darling.
    205.19
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Restaurant Facilities - Miscellaneous - F. W. Darling, 1933-1934 (Box 96, Folder 723)
    Hired to plan activities on 65th floor; policy disagreement.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Restaurant Facilities - Miscellaneous - Promenade Caf, 1936 (Box 96, Folder 724)
    Opening program for benefit of charity in Cafe.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Affiliated Corporations, 1934-1949 (Box 97, Folder 725)
    Organization of Centroc, Center Music Hall, Inc., Center Services, Inc., Center Restaurants, Inc., Center Publications, Inc. Affairs of corporations; meetings. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, B. P. Turnbull.
    205.20
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Affiliated Corporations - Center Music Hall, 1934-1942 (Box 97, Folder 726)
    Minutes.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Affiliated Corporations - Rockefeller Center Warehouses, Inc., 1935-1947 (Box 97, Folder 727)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Affiliated Corporations - Centroc, 1934-1949 (Box 97, Folder 728)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Affiliated Corporations - Center Services, 1939-1949 (Box 97, Folder 729)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Affiliated Corporations - Exhibition of Decorative Arts, 1937-1956 (Box 97, Folder 730)
    Management of home furniture display; Nelson A. Rockefeller interest.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Management Organization and Committees, 1934 (Box 97, Folder 731)
    Relations between officers of Rockefeller Center, Inc. and Managing Agents; problems in communications. Rockefeller brothers service on committees. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, J. R. Todd.
    205.21
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Management Organization and Committees, 1935-1940 (Box 97, Folder 732)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Management Reorganization, 1938 (Box 97, Folder 733)
    Retirement of Todd and Brown as managers; organization of new management committees. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    205.21A
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Reorganization, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 734)
    Nelson A. Rockefeller made president upon death of Turnbull; H. S. Robertson resigned; G. S. Eyssell made Executive Manager.
    205.21B
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Exhibitions, 1934-1960 (Box 98, Folder 735)
    Ideas for exhibitions in Center, ranging from costumes and home interiors to photographs on war; most declined by Center management. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Charles O. Heydt, B. P. Turnbull.
    205.22
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Exhibitions - Salons of America, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 736)
    Art show; purchase of some items by Nelson A. Rockefeller and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Exhibitions - Municipal Art Show, 1933-1934 (Box 98, Folder 737)
    Held in Center; report on success.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Exhibitions - Fine Arts Exhibition, 1934 (Box 98, Folder 738)
    Publicity for show.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Exhibitions - Dr. M. Therese Bonney, 1935 (Box 98, Folder 739)
    Exhibition of French art in French Building.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Legal Department and Services, 1936-1939 (Box 98, Folder 740)
    Legal opinions on leases, taxes, employment arrangements, accident claims against Rockefeller Center, Inc.. Correspondents include Thomas M. Debevoise, Francis T. Christy.
    205.23
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Legal Department and Services, 1940-1956 (Box 98, Folder 741)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Legal Department and Services - Milbank Tweed Bills, 1932-1939 (Box 98, Folder 742)
    Authorizations to pay legal fees.
    Restricted - Legal or financial records.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Legal Department and Services - Adderley Correspondence, 1937-1948 (Box 98, Folder 743)
    Tributes to him from Nelson A. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Legal Department and Services - Restaurants, Arts, Music, 1939-1944 (Box 98, Folder 744)
    Successful attempt to eliminate paying social security taxes on restaurant entertainers' salaries.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Planting and Roof Garden - Mr. Hancock, 1935-1950 (Box 99, Folder 745)
    Plans for gardens; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. appreciation of gardens. Comments. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., A. M. Van den Hoek.
    205.24
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Planting and Roof Garden - Appreciation of Trees, 1939-1951 (Box 99, Folder 746)
    Letters of appreciation for trees around Center.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Planning Committee, 1935-1937 (Box 99, Folder 747)
    Discussion of location and signs on Radio Corporation of America (RCA) Building. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Thomas M. Debevoise.
    205.26
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Theater Passes, 1930-1960 (Box 99, Folder 748)
    Sending of annual passes to theaters, National Broadcasting Company (NBC) Studios and observation roof to members of the family.
    205.27
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees
    Employee problems; retirements; complaints; industrial relations. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas M. Debevoise, Victor Borella, Frank Staley.
    205.28
    - Employees, 1934-1938 (Box 99, Folder 749)
    - Employees, 1939-1961 (Box 99, Folder 749A)
    - Employees, 1942-1947 (Box 99, Folder 750)
    - Employees, 1948-1961 (Box 99, Folder 751)
    - Employees, 1940-1961 (Box 99, Folder 751A)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Strike, 1943 (Box 100, Folder 752)
    Jurisdictional strike, quickly ended.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Industrial Relations, 1933-1939 (Box 100, Folder 753)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Winthrop Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller interest in personnel problems.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Winthrop Rockefeller Report on Industrial Relations, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 754)
    Winthrop Rockefeller suggested program for Rockefeller Center.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Medical Department, 1938-1949 (Box 100, Folder 755)
    Reports on operations.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Charles McCarthy, 1939-1959 (Box 100, Folder 756)
    Doorman; retirement.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. re Labor Policy, 1938-1940 (Box 100, Folder 757)
    Emphasis on personal relation in industry.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Twenty-Year Club, 1953-1961 (Box 100, Folder 758)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - W. K. Harrison, 1944-1947 (Box 100, Folder 759)
    Appointed as consulting architect.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Hugh W. Robertson, 1941-1949 (Box 100, Folder 760)
    Contract; illness; resignation.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Gymnasium, 1934-1951 (Box 100, Folder 761)
    Opening exercises at gymnasium; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. address. Invitations to dances and parties. Correspondents include Victor Borella, Nelson A. Rockefeller, H. S. Robertson, B. P. Turnbull, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Employees - Borella, 1939-1947 (Box 100, Folder 762)
    Employee programs; relations. Wartime service; promotion. Correspondents include Victor Borella, Nelson A. Rockefeller, B. P. Turnbull.
    205.282
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Labor Union Contracts, 1937-1947 (Box 101, Folder 763)
    Contract negotiations; agreements. Changing pattern of union demands. Correspondents include Victor Borella, Nelson A. Rockefeller. H. S. Robertson, B. P. Turnbull.
    205.281
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Annuity Plan - Group Insurance, 1939-1959 (Box 101, Folder 764)
    Development of pension plan; modifications. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Victor Borella.
    205.29
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Annuity Plan - Group Insurance - Hugh S. Robertson Pension, 1941-1951 (Box 101, Folder 765)
    Arrangements of managerial contract with pension future built in. Robertson's death.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Annuity Plan - Group Insurance - Authorization, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 766)
    Directors' approval of plan.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Letters of Appreciation, 1938-1955 (Box 101, Folder 767)
    Letters to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Nelson A. Rockefeller about pleasure gained from Center. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    205.30
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Awards, 1938-1940 (Box 101, Folder 768)
    Awards to Center for architectural beauty and for trees. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    205.31
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Radio Program, South America, 1940-1941 (Box 101, Folder 769)
    Music Hall shortwave programs via National Broadcasting Company (NBC); discussion of costs; Nelson A. Rockefeller's interest. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Victor Borella.
    205.32
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1930-1932 (Box 102, Folder 770)
    Printed copies of basic lease and underwriting documents: Agreements with Trustees of Columbia University, and with Radio Corporation of America (RCA), Radio-Keith-Orpheum (RKO); Chase Bank Agreements; Architects Agreements; Metropolitan Life Insurance Company Agreements; Underel Corporation Agreements.
    205.34
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1933-1937 (Box 102, Folder 771)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1928-1931 (Box 102, Folder 772)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1928-1951 (Box 102, Folder 773)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1928-1931 (Box 102, Folder 774)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1939-1955 (Box 103, Folder 775)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1928 (Box 103, Folder 776)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1928 (Box 103, Folder 777)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1931-1936 (Box 103, Folder 778)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1930 (Box 103, Folder 779)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1930-1941 (Box 104, Folder 780)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Documents, 1931-1947 (Box 104, Folder 781)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Atomic Defense Plan, 1950-1961 (Box 104, Folder 782)
    Plans for protection against fall-out; changes between 1950 and 1961. Survey of shelter areas. Minutes of Civil Defense Committee. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, G. S. Eyssell.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Possible Merger, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 783)
    Analysis of proposed merger with Atlas Corporation; no follow-up. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
    205.35
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Possible Merger, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 0783A)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Zeckendorf Hotel Proposal, 1958-1959 (Box 105, Folder 784)
    Proposed hotel on 6th Avenue between 51st and 52nd Streets. Zeckendorf made initial proposal; study of possibilities; Dilworth skeptical. Decision against proposal. Sheraton Corporation proposal for hotel, 1960; sale of land to Uris Corporation. Correspondents include William Zeckendorf, J. R. Dilworth.
    205.37
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Zeckendorf Hotel Proposal, 1958-1959 (Box 105, Folder 785)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - New Time and Life Tower Building, 1955-1961 (Box 105, Folder 786)
    Center proposed letter to Time, Inc. re new building; planning; construction and publicity. Opening; sidewalk superintendents club. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, G. Eyssell, J. R. Dilworth.
    205.38
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - New Time and Life Tower Building - Cornerstone, 1959 (Box 105, Folder 787)
    Arrangements and invitations.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - New Time and Life Tower Building - Hemisphere Club, 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 788)
    Luncheon Club on 48th floor of Time-Life Building.
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Uris Brothers, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 789)
    Uris Brothers plan to build hotel on 6th Avenue between 53rd and 54th Streets on land purchased from Zeckendorf; agreement between Rockefeller Center, Inc., Uris and Hilton Hotels to build and operate hotel. Financing construction; tie-in with Uris office building. Correspondents include J. Dilworth, G. S. Eyssell, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    205.500
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Uris Brothers, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 790)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Uris Brothers, October 1960-January 1961 (Box 106, Folder 791)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Uris Brothers, August-September 1960 (Box 106, Folder 792)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Hil-Uris, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 793)
    Corporation organized to build and operate new hotel. Comments on architecture by Harrison and Abramovitz. Correspondents include W. K. Harrison, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    205.600
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Metropolitan Square Corporation - Architects, 1928-1929 (Box 106, Folder 794)